

TRAN VAN AN

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

**** 0981 550 870

□ an.tran.itpnv@gmail.com

↑ 267 Hai Phong Street, Hai Chau District, Da Nang City

EDUCATION

Passerelles Numériques Vietnam 2015 - 2017

Associated Degree in IT issued by Da Nang College of Technology and Passerelles Numériques certificate.

> LogiGear Company 2016 - 2017

Manual Testing and Automation Testing Certification

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS & Bootstrap
- JavaScript & jQuery
- PHP & framework (CakePHP & Laravel)
- MySQL
- Photoshop
- Testing
- Microsoft Office: Word, Excel. PowerPoint

SOFT SKILLS

- Strong communication
- Ability to work in a team
- Good time management
- Disciplined

ENGLISH SKILLS

• Pre-intermediate proficiency

INTERESTS

- Sport
- Cooking
- Researching

ABOUT

I am a student at Passerelles Numériques Vietnam and my major is Web Development and Testing. I desire to work for a well-known company such as yours where I can contribute my best. I strongly believe my work experience, soft skills and passion for web developer position would bring value to your company.

PROFESSIONAL PROJECT

PROJECT WITH SIOUX COMPANY

Housing helpers service website

Mar 2017 - May 2017

- Built a website by Cake PHP framework, Bootstrap, MySQL and used Sublime Text tool to develop website.
- Applied Scrum Model to manage project.
- Added features: Login, register, admin page, upload image, tested and edited websites.
- Communicated with team members in a professional manner.
- Link: http://wonderteam.esy.es/

DEVELOP A WEBSITE BY CAKE PHP FRAMEWORK

Sale motorbike website

Nov 2016 - Nov 2016

- Built an e-commerce website by Cake PHP framework, Bootstrap, MySQL and using Sublime Text tool to develop website.
- Created a database using for Cake PHP.
- Added featers: Add cart, pay cart for products, tested and edited websites
- Link: github.com/TranAnIT/sale-motorbike

WORK EXPERIENCE

DN COFFEE WEBSITE

Agility Company

Mar 2017 - Aug 2017

- Built a website by Laravel framework, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, applied Sass and used Visual Studio Code tool to develop website.
- Wrote SRS, designed UI Mockup.
- Added features: Login, register, add products, show products, add to cart, search, tested and edited website.
- Link: https://TranAnIT@bitbucket.org/antraninternship/fcoffee-project.git

ENGLISH E-BOOK

Softech Company

June 2016 - July 2016

- Used Adobe Flash tool to designed interactive English lesson books.
- Used WebStorm tool to built code HTML, CSS.
- Extracted images and replicated sounds using Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator and Adobe Audition.
- Communicated with team members in a professional manner.
- Conducted and completed projects in a timely fashion.

REFERENCES

- Name: Vo Cong Dinh.
- Position: IT teacher Passerelles numeriques Vietnam.
- Email: dinh.cong@passerellesnumeriques.org.